(Wil:)And then I don't get the job,
and I can never find out why.
(Wil:)Honestly, I get so depressed,
there are entire weeks
(Wil:)that I can't even get out of bed.
(Leonard:)Okay, this was helpful.
(Raj:)Any news on your co-worker
who's in the hospital?
(Bernadette:)Poor thing,
she was in surgery for 18 hours.
(Bernadette:)She's alive, but she's
still in critical condition.
(Raj:)Oh, no.
(Bernadette:)The one bit of good news
is they put her
(Bernadette:)in a medically induced coma
before she read the card.
(Bernadette:)So, you know, silver linings.
(Howard:)Were you like this
when I married you?
(Leonard(on phone):)Don't worry about it, buddy.
(Leonard(on phone):)-Okay, bye.
(Leonard(on phone):)That was Wil,
he's feeling a lot better.
(Leonard(on phone):)Apparently, he's 12-down
in the TV Guide crossword puzzle.
(Raj:)Did he help you make a decision
about the movie?